One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
you'll have to be tough.
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
Arrival at Coral Hill!
The Nosebleed and the Devastating Prediction!
Sanji-chan!
Rejoice!
I...
will...
live here!
Sanji-chan, you're so funny!
Looks like he's back to his old self now that he's here.
Is it pure willpower?
You guys are so lucky, being able to swim and all.
Luffy-chin, you can swim too if you use a bubble.
Really?!
Anyway, I'm relieved.
If he gets another nosebleed, I won't
be able to treat him since I'm out of blood bags.
Sanji has a rare blood type, after all.
Hey, Caimie...
There's someone here on Fishman Island
I really want to meet!
Who is it? The Mermaid Princess?
Nope!
It's Jinbe!
Boss Jinbe?
W-Wait, Luffy, when you say Jinbe...
You didn't befriend another Warlord, did you?!
Oh, wait, he quit during the war,
so I guess he's an ex-Warlord now.
Yup! He's my friend!
W-What is it with you?!
Fishman Island "Ryuuguu Kingdom"
After Ace died two years ago...
the only reason I got back on my feet
was because he helped me!
I really wanna meet Jinbe!
Let us meet again in two years, at Fishman Island!
I am looking forward to the day when you and your crew arrive!
I promised I'd meet him on this island!
Now that you mention it,
I read an article that said you were with Boss Jinbe.
Where is Jinbe?
Uh... Well, he isn't on the island.
Huh?
You know how he resigned from the Seven Warlords of the Sea during the war two years ago?
Because of that, the former members of the
Fishman Pirates couldn't stay on this island anymore.
So they all left, together with Boss Jinbe.
Huh?! So does that mean I can't see him?
It's a long story, but basically the war had a great impact on this island too.
Caimie!
A ship is coming!
It might be coming!
A royal ship is coming!
Maybe nobody's on it!
Of course there's somebody on it!
Who's onboard the ship, Killifish-chins?
We don't know yet.
The royal ship, such a rare sight!
A ship that hardly ever comes here!
Maybe they're here to arrest Luffy-chin and the others, since they're illegal immigrants?
So what if they are?
You all have to hide, Luffy-chin!
Is that the royal family's gondola?
Is it really?
It is!
Isn't it?
It is, isn't it?
So what if it is?
But it can't actually be
someone from the royal family, can it?
They wouldn't come all the way
out to this corner of the island themselves.
The three Neptune Brothers have arrived!
Greetings, women of the cove.
Ryuuguu Kingdom
The Three Brothers of the Neptune Family
There is something I would like to ask.
It's the princes!
What are they doing here?!
Princes?
No, Sanji-chan!
A-Alright.
You have to stay hidden.
Hey, what's...
We have received word of some illegal immigrants.
First son - Fukaboshi
(Shark Merman)
Did they come this way?
If they did, then please say so-la-ti-do!
Second son - Ryuboshi
(Oarfish Merman)
If they didn't, then that's alright too-mi-re-do!
Akkamanbo! Yay! Yay!
Third son - Manboshi
(Opah Merman)
I wanna have some fun here too!
Nobody has come this way.
Are they really so important?
I mean, for you princes to come all the way out here...
Well, we haven't yet confirmed whether or not
they are who I think they are.
We haven't confirmed it-mi-re-do!
Everyone! Let's dance together!
What's all the commotion about?
Hey, those are the princes from the Neptune Army!
What are they doing here?
This is a problem.
I see. Thank you for your assistance.
We will look elsewhere.
Forgive us for disturbing you while you were having such a good time.
Let's have another dance sometime!
Sorry for disturbing you-fa-mi-re-do!
Not at all!
Did the border police make a mistake?
Sanji!
Sanji-chan!
All that blood... Sanji's in trouble!
It didn't work!
All the excitement he was holding in erupted!
That's...
No doubt about it. That's the pirate Straw Hat Luffy.
Ammo Knights!
Yes, Sir!
Whaddayaknow, Straw Hat and his group are here.
What are we gonna do?
The army will get them before us!
But it's a bad idea to fight the Neptune Army here.
Please, wait!
We're sorry about entering the country illegally!
But if you're gonna arrest us, please do it later!
Is there anyone here willing to donate their blood?!
Without help, our companion will be dead within an hour!
He has blood type S, RH-.
It's not very common,
but is there anyone here with that type?!
Or do mermen and fishmen have different blood from humans?
Chopper-chin...
Hurry! Isn't there anyone?!
You can't... You can't die such a ridiculous death!
Please, anyone! I'm begging you!
Give Sanji blood!
Luffy-chin, Chopper-chin!
Both mermen and fishmen have
the same blood types as humans.
It's possible to do a blood transfusion.
But...
These humans are spouting nonsense!
It's the guys with the sea monsters!
Prince Fukaboshi,
it's Hammond of the Fishman District.
Give our blood to an inferior species like you humans?
Nobody on Fishman Island would be so obliging!
And even if you found someone...
the human-haters on this island would
subject them to the Judgment of the Dark Night!
That kid can just lie there and bleed to death.
He's completely beyond help!
There is an old law in this country...
"You shall not share your blood with humans."
What?!
Make no mistake!
This law was created by you humans.
During our long history together,
you humans have always feared us as monsters!
You were the ones
who forbade the mixing of our blood!
That is what caused the death of
Fishman Island's hero, Fisher Tiger.
The man who put his life on the line to
free all slaves, regardless of their species.
He died after a bloody battle, even though he could have easily been saved by a blood transfusion!
The heartless humans refused to give him blood...
so he died!
Disregard the life of that one underling of yours, and come with us to the Fishman District!
The captain of the New Fishman Pirates, Hody Jones-sama, wants to see you!
Hey, I don't know anything about your rules, but please,
isn't there anyone here with the blood type S, RH-?!
We don't care what we have to do in return!
For now, please just save his life!
Camie!
If you're not gonna come willingly...
We'll just have to bring you along by force!
Trawl Net!
I thought I already told you...
I won't...
do what you say!
Jet Pistol!
Luffy! There's a sea monster behind you!
Hammond and his gang from the Fishman District...
The sea monster...
admitted defeat without even fighting?!
Amazing!
What was that? Luffy-chan is amazing!
I would expect no less.
Luffy-chin!
Bring Sanji-chin aboard!
Let's go to the city!
There are plenty of humans at the port in the city!
Hurry!
You there, wait!
The Ryuuguu belongs to the princes!
I'm sorry! I promise to give it back after we've saved Sanji-chin!
Right, we're aboard! Caimie, let's go!
Please Ryuuguu-chin! Take us to the city!
I'm so sorry.
If only I had the same blood type, I would gladly help.
You have nothing to apologize for.
It's his fault for having
perverted thoughts in the first place.
Just look! He's still grinning.
Sanji! Just stop it, already!
Don't imagine anything at all!
We don't have a second to spare!
Still, this reminds me of the discrimination that
you and Hachi suffered on Sabaody two years ago.
It looks like the problem runs deep.
I never thought a nosebleed could become something serious like this.
Yeah... Even if we get to the city,
I'm still a bit worried.
Will we find someone willing to donate blood on time?
In the past month,
no humans have come to the island at all.
You are the first guests we've had in a while.
Why? Isn't this a famous tourist spot?
Yeah, it is, but...
We don't know for sure, but there's a rumor that something is interfering with travelers' voyages.
That there's some shadowy force behind all of this... People all over the country are talking about it.
This is quite inconvenient, you know.
Why were you hiding the pirates from us?
We're so sorry, Prince Fukaboshi!
Caimie said they were her friends.
They weren't bad people, so we didn't want them to be arrested as illegal immigrants.
Will Sanji-chan really be alright?
You're jumping to conclusions. They are famous pirates.
It doesn't matter how they entered the country.
We were already perfectly aware who they are.
We were looking for them
for a different reason-re-mi-fa!
Really?
I didn't get a chance to give them...
Jinbe's message.
Ryuuguu Kingdom, Port Town
"Coral Hill"
Sanji! Are you awake?
Sanji-chin!
Where am I?
Thank goodness!
We're in the house of one of my friends from the port town.
Sanji-chin, you'd lost
most of the blood in your body!
I'm so glad we were able to find
a donor with the same blood type!
I see... My blood, huh?
What happened to me?
You mustn't get up so suddenly! Stay in bed.
But really, why did the fishmen refuse to give him blood?
We ran all over town,
but we couldn't find any humans!
I honestly thought it was hopeless!
Thanks for helping me, you guys.
But... I can't remember a thing.
Where was I, and what was I doing?
If you get another nosebleed, you'll be beyond saving!
Oh, right! Sanji, let me introduce
the blood donors we met at the bar!
You mean I was given blood by... a delicate lady?
It's quite alright...
We humans need to help each other out in times of need.
It's alright, silly.
Pirate Twins
Splash and Splatter
If you like, we'll gladly give you more, silly.
I'm glad you've recovered.
Come on, thank them already.
Luffy. Let me see your right arm for a second.
A poison reaction...
That wound is poisoned.
Oh yeah, while I was fighting the fishmen earlier...
I did feel a slight sting.
And you're completely fine?!
This poison is lethal!
That's amazing!
Luffy's body must have developed antitoxins, and repelled the poison without us noticing!
Have you been exposed to
large amounts of poison before?
Poison, huh...
I was almost killed by poison back in Impel Down.
Almost killed?
Is that really something to laugh about?!
It must have been that guy...
The swordsman with the octopus-legs.
He withstood my attack, after all.
He was pretty tough.
That came from the cove.
Those mermaids sure are noisy.
Now then, what should I do?
These guys are both out cold.
And I carelessly ended up poisoning Straw Hat.
Assassin of the New Fishman Pirates
Hyouzou (Blue-Ringed Octopus Merman)
It'd be real bad if he died.
That scream was from Ishilly and the others, right?
Ishilly!
I'm sure I heard them over here.
Where could they have gone?
Earlier, I heard them talking about opening a barrel.
The manager of the Mermaid Café. She let us borrow the room.
What's this?!
This is Madame Shyarly.
Really? Thanks!
Is the blond boy alright now?
Owner of the Mermaid Cafe
Madame Shyarly
Yeah.
But Madame, since you're so beautiful,
you should stay out of his room for now.
Also, the fact that we're in the back rooms
of the Mermaid Café...
Keep it a secret from Sanji-chin.
Why?
Because if he finds out...
he'll be in trouble again,
or so his doctor, Chopper-chin, says.
That's an odd prescription.
Hey! Huge mermaid!
Her name is Madame Shyarly, Luffy-chin!
What's this?
It's so pretty!
Don't touch that, Straw Hat Boy.
Huh?
That's a crystal ball. It's used for fortune-telling.
Madame is famous for
making predictions here on Coral Hill.
I've quit fortune-telling.
It's better not to know the future.
So, do mermaids poop?
Whaddaya mean, "so"?!
That has nothing to do with fortune-telling!
You vulgar boy!
Apologize to her, Luffy-chin!
Sorry!
Caimie...
Feel free to take the day off.
Give your friends a tour of the island.
Are you sure?
You've been working really hard, after all.
Besides...
Lately, we haven't gotten a single human pirate customer.
This will be good for business.
The girls from the cove will be coming here soon, so we've got more than enough staff.
Oh, that reminds me!
I have to hurry and give Pappagg his clams!
That's one weird way to realize that.
He must be starving.
What?
If you mean Monsieur Pappagg, he met an old friend of his.
The two of them are hanging out in the café right now.
I didn't mention this earlier but...
Back when the Madame was still a child,
she said that lots of pirates
would be coming to the island soon...
And then the Great Age of Pirates began the following year.
What?!
It'd take way too long if I told you all the details,
but a while back she also predicted
the war at Marineford and the death of Whitebeard.
Since she's predicted so many bad things, it sounds like she's gotten tired of it.
That's scary!
Wait, where's Chopper?
He's looking after Sanji.
Luffy-chin, Usopp-chin!
Coming!
This is the main street on Coral Hill.
Look! This is the entrance to the Mermaid Café!
Man, I sure am hungry!
It's just a café!
We have food here too.
Like cake and fruits of the sea!
How about meat?
Merfolk don't eat meat or fish, so...
the menu consists of Seaweed Brûlée, Algae Tart, Kelp Soufflé...
Is any of that good?
But we do have meat too!
Really?!
Shellfish meat, Scallop Sandwich, Freshwater Clam Pizza-
Shellfish meat doesn't count! Don't insult meat like that!
Anyway, let's get going. To the Mermaid Café.
Yeah. Pappagg's waiting for us.
I mean it! Don't look down on meat!
Thank you very much!
Brook!
Brook-chin!
Oh? Why, if it isn't Luffy-san!
And Caimie-san, it has been far too long!
Straw! Nose!
I've really missed you guys!
So you're finally here?
So you were with Pappagg?
Please come again, Soul King!
It feels like we've been living a dream!
I'm definitely comin' back, beautiful mermaids!
What?
I need to loosen my bones a little.
Ah! But if I were to loosen my bones, I'd die!
I wouldn't mind dying right now! Though I already am dead.
Amazing!
They've just been in a café,
yet the tension is already this high?
You're right! What's it like in there?
Now, wait just a minute!
It's not like you're leaving today, is it?
I understand why you're interested,
but later you can all go to the Mermaid Café together.
I was just about to take Bones on a tour of my mansion!
Follow me! Do you like the meat of sea beasts?
You have meat?!
You think a wild man such as myself
would be satisfied with seashells and seaweed?
My diet consists of
the meat of the very fiercest sea beasts!
Oh, Pappagg, I forgot!
Here are your clams for today.
Yay! Caimie's delicious clams!
Hey, aren't those just shellfish?!
Merfolk don't eat meat and fish, but fishmen do.
So it's not like there isn't any of it on this island.
Really? That's a relief!
Hey, taxi!
Vander Decken?!
Why is a ghost on the wanted list?
The guy from the ghost ship we met on the way here?
Huh? You met him?!
He's some kind of undersea robber who
the country has been hunting down for ages.
But let's talk about that later. For now, get onboard!
Vander Decken used to send a love letter to the Mermaid Princess of Ryuuguu Kingdom every week.
Eventually he went from letters to packages,
and then threats and demands for her to marry him.
This is so fluffy! It feels so nice!
This truly feels like paradise!
Listen to what I'm saying!
Sure!
Oh, excuse me.
The princess was terrified...
and the country could no longer ignore it, so...
Indeed! The princess' father, King Neptune, got upset,
and the three princes you met earlier mobilized the army to chase after him,
but they couldn't find him.
Caimie... Caimie... I was just about to explain that.
So basically, King Neptune the Sea God,
who rules this country,
has four children including the Mermaid Princess.
The Mermaid Princess is the youngest, and her
big brothers are the three princes you met earlier.
Uh, but something bothers me.
Isn't Vander Decken that cursed pirate from several hundred years ago?
Oh!
Well, legends are often
exaggerations of exaggerations.
It seems that he did exist,
but the Vander Decken from the legend was just a man who reached this island and lived in the country.
So, the ship you encountered
was probably the real Flying Dutchman...
but the captain was just his descendant!
Va-
Vander Decken the ninth!
What?! His descendant?!
Fish Taxi
Oh, that's how it is? So he wasn't a ghost after all.
Being only bones, and thinking I had met a real ghost, I was starting to feel more dead than alive.
Thank goodness.
If nothing else, I am truly happy about that.
Caimie... Caimie... Caimie...
Oh! Now that I look closely, there are
so many different kinds of merfolk and fishmen!
There are old lady mermaids down there too!
They're just like old Kokoro!
Look over there! Those are babies!
Their father is a fishman,
but his kids are both merfolk and fishmen.
Basically, if a fishman and a mermaid get married, they can have sons and daughters of either race.
In other words, there are four possible outcomes.
So that's why there are so many different types!
That's cool!
We're getting on the high-speed current now.
This is so fast!
Huh? What's that?
Ah, that's the candy factory.
That's not what I meant.
Why is there a pirate-flag on it?
Oh, that? There's one at the bay
and at the entrance to the island too.
Fishman Island is currently
under the protection of that pirate flag.
It's the mark of the New World pirate
Charlotte Linlin.
Also known as Big Mom. One of the Four Emperors!
Before the war, this island was protected from pirates by Whitebeard's name.
Now, Big Mom is watching over it.
Really?
In exchange, we have to give her
large amounts of candy every month.
That's what the factory is for.
Candy?
If we're not protected by someone great like that,
the country would never survive.
It would become too dangerous here, since it's like the pirates' highway.
But if this Big Mom is protecting you in old man Whitebeard's place, she must be nice, right?
Hard to say... At least Whitebeard never asked for compensation.
Perhaps Big Mom just thinks of it like business?
Big Mom, huh? One of the Four Emperors,
just like Shanks.
I wonder if I'll meet her someday?
Look up ahead!
We have reached the city of celebrities,
Fishverly Hills!
That huge building right in front of us
is Pappagg's house!
That?! But he's just a starfish!
Coral Hill
This is bad.
Isn't that the Madame from the Mermaid Café?
What's wrong, Madame Shyarly?
Why are you so upset?
If we don't act quickly, something terrible will happen!
Hey, Madame... What do you mean?
Go look for him!
The pirate-boy wearing a straw hat...
Chase him out of the kingdom, right now!
Is this another prediction?
I didn't intend to look...
but I felt something from him, and ended up taking a peek...
at his future!
What's wrong?! What did you see?!
Madame?!
Shyarly?!
Let it be wrong! Please, let my prediction be wrong!
The human with the straw hat...
Straw Hat Luffy...
By his hands...
Fishman Island will...
be destroyed!